Hello. I'm } with Expert Village.
And, we're talking today about numerology.
And, today, I'm going to demonstrate to you
how to calculate your birth number. So, my
friend, }, popped in and offered to be the
subject for this demonstration. Hi, everybody.
Thank you, }. Thank you, Carmen. How are
you? Good. Good. So, } is going to tell
us what his birthday is and from that I'm
going to demonstrate to you how to calculate
his birth number. So, }, what is your birthday?
} }, }. Okay. So, I'm going to
show you how to do this. Okay. So, we have
} }, }. So, } is }, the
second month. We have }. And we have }.
So, how numerology works is you keep adding
together. So, 2, that's just one digit. }
is 2 plus 8. } is 1 plus 9 plus 5 plus
4. What do these equal? 2 is 2. 2 plus 8 equals
10. 1 plus 9 plus 5 plus 4. What does that
equal? 1 plus 9 is 10 plus 5 is 15 plus 4
is 19. 19. And, then we keep adding again.
We've got 2. We've got 10. And, we've got
19. 2 is 2. 10, 1 plus 0, 1. Okay. 1 plus
9. What's one plus nine? 10. Good. Thank you,
}. You're good at math. And then, okay,
we keep adding for the final time. We've got
2. We've got 1. 1 plus 0, what is that? One.
Excellent. So, now we have our final three
numbers. 2 plus 1 plus 1. And, that equals?
Three. Four. Excuse me. I know that was a
deliberate mistake. Okay. So, 4. We have discovered
}'s life number, his birth date number.
And, that is 4.